http://www.winesandvines.com/privacy

Privacy Policy
This policy describes the privacy practices of Wines & Vines Magazine and is referred to herein as 'Wines & Vines'. This Privacy Policy is applicable only to Wines & Vines and does not apply to the print versions of the Wines & Vines Magazine or Directory/Buyer's Guide. This policy does not apply to any third party web sites or to companies or persons not controlled by, affiliated with or managed by Wines & Vines and applies only to information collected by Wines & Vines on the Wines & Vines website and not to information disclosed, obtained or used by Wines & Vines through other means. Wines & Vines may provide links to unaffiliated websites for which this privacy does not apply. If you are unsure whether a website is controlled, affiliated or managed by Wines & Vines, we recommend that you review the privacy policy at each linked web site to determine how that site treats your personal information.
Wines & Vines may change this privacy policy from time to time. Please check this page periodically for changes.
INFORMATION COLLECTED
Customer Information
Wines & Vines collects basic contact information and basic industry information regarding the customer's role within the wine industry. We compile all customer information to efficiently provide the most effective content on winesandvines.com. We retain the right to make this information available to our partners and affiliates periodically.
Subscriber Information
All subscribers of the Wines & Vines Magazine are provided access to specified content that would not be accessible otherwise. Subscriber information is not kept on the website, nor is it updateable. The subscriber information to login to the website is obtained after purchasing a product from Wines & Vines (http://www.winesandvines.com/template.cfm?section=subscribe).
Directory/Buyer's Guide
All purchasers of the Directory/Buyer's Guide are provided access to specified content that would not be accessible otherwise. Buyer's information of this product is not kept on the website, nor is it updateable. The login information to the website is obtained after purchasing the product from Wines & Vines (http://www.winesandvines.com/template.cfm?section=subscribe).
Online Commerce
The Wines & Vines website collects billing information upon purchase of a Wines & Vines product and uses SSL encryption for all billing and shipping information. Wines & Vines does not store credit card encrypted or unencrypted credit card information other than the last 4 digits of a customer's credit card upon successful completion of an order.
Cookies
Wines & Vines use of cookies is intended for the convenience of visitors to the www.winesandvines.com website. Wines & Vines subscribers' access to premium editorial content on-line, including the ability to post comments, is controlled via login. Cookies enable users' login parameters to be saved, making it unnecessary to log in again on successive visits to the website. Similarly, cookies ease navigation of the online directory by remembering a user's most recent search results.
Public Comments
Information posted by you the user to winesandvines.com becomes public information. Please use caution when posting information to the website and do not post sensitive personal information.
If posting a comment while logged into winesandvines.com you have the option of posting with your full name or with an alias. Please note that we are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit to the website.
Hyperlinks
Winesandvines.com contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Wines & Vines. Wines & Vines is not liable for any content, products, privacy policies or other materials available on these sites.
Security
Wines & Vines uses procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access to the information collected on the Winesandvines.com. Although such protective measures have been put in place, Wines & Vines cannot ensure that the information collected will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy.
TERMS OF USE
The Winesandvines.com site contains material that is protected by copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. Unless otherwise specified, the site and all content on the site are intended for your personal, noncommercial use only. You may not modify, copy, reproduce, republish, upload, post, transmit, or distribute in any way any material from the site except as provided in this Terms of Use. You may download material from the site and may use the site for your personal, non-commercial use only, provided you keep intact all copyright and other proprietary notices. You may not republish any content from the site, distribute any content to others, modify, sell or otherwise use the content or decompile, reverse engineer or disassemble any software or other products or processes accessible at the site. Your license to use the site is contingent upon your compliance with these Terms of Use.
You agree to use the site in accordance with these Terms of Use. Accessing the site, in any manner, for the purpose of obtaining information, technical or otherwise, constitutes use of the site such that these Terms of Use bind the party accessing the site. Wines & Vines may need to change these Terms of Use or impose new conditions on use of the site, from time to time, in which case we will post the revised Terms of Use on the site. By continuing to use the site after we post any such changes, you accept the Terms of Use, as modified.
You may establish a hypertext link to the site so long as the link does not state or imply any sponsorship of your site by Wines & Vines. However, you may not, without the prior written permission of Wines & Vines frame any of the content of the site, or incorporate into another website any material from the site.
License to Wines & Vines
By posting messages, or uploading files, or otherwise providing any material for display on the site, you are representing that you are the owner of the material, or are making your submission with the consent of the owner of the material, all information you provide is true, accurate, current and complete and does not violate these Terms of Use. In addition, when you post a message, upload a file, or otherwise provide us with material for display on the site, you are granting Wines & Vines a perpetual, irrevocable, royalty-free, non-exclusive license, with the right to use, copy, sublicense, modify, adapt, transmit, distribute, publicly perform or display such material. The foregoing grants shall include the right to exploit any proprietary rights in such material, including but not limited to rights under copyright, trademark, service mark or patent laws in any jurisdiction. All rights in this paragraph are granted without compensation of any sort to you.
DISCLAIMERS AND LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
The Sites include links and pointers to Internet sites, content and services provided by third parties. Wines & Vines linking to any third party sites does not imply an endorsement or sponsorship of such sites or the information, products or services offered on or through the sites. In addition, Wines & Vines does not operate or control in any respect any information, products or services that third parties may provide on or through the site or on web sites linked to by Wines & Vines.
USE OF THE SITES IS AT YOUR OWN RISK. THE MATERIALS, INFORMATION, PRODUCTS AND SERVICES OFFERED ON OR THROUGH THE SITES AND ANY THIRD-PARTY SITES ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE PURSUANT TO APPLICABLE LAW, Wines & Vines DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. Wines & Vines DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE SITES OR ANY OF ITS FUNCTIONS WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR-FREE, THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT ANY PART OF THE SITES, INCLUDING BULLETIN BOARDS, OR THE SERVERS THAT MAKE SERVICES AVAILABLE, ARE FREE OF VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. YOU ASSUME THE ENTIRE COST OF ALL NECESSARY MAINTENANCE, REPAIR OR CORRECTION. Wines & Vines DOES NOT WARRANT OR MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS REGARDING THE USE OR THE RESULTS OF THE USE OF THE SITES OR MATERIALS ON THE SITES OR ON THIRD-PARTY SITES IN TERMS OF THEIR CORRECTNESS, ACCURACY, TIMELINESS, RELIABILITY OR OTHERWISE. Wines & Vines ASSUMES NO LIABILITY FOR THE CONTENT OF THE SITES, DOES NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT USE OF THE CONTENT WILL NOT INFRINGE RIGHTS OF THIRD PARTIES AND Wines & Vines HAS NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY OF ACTIONS OF THIRD PARTIES OR FOR CONTENT PROVIDED BY OTHERS. IN NO EVENT SHALL Wines & Vines, ITS AFFILIATES EMPLOYEES, AGENTS OR CONTENT PROVIDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES, EVEN IF ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, OR FOR ANY AMOUNT OF DIRECT DAMAGES IN EXCESS OF $100. (Since some states do not allow the exclusion or limitation of certain categories of damages, the above limitation many not apply to you. In such states, the liability of Wines & Vines is limited to the fullest extent permitted by such state law.)
The site may contain facts, views, opinions, statements and recommendations of third party individuals and organizations. Wines & Vines does not represent or endorse the accuracy or reliability of any advice, opinion, statement or other information on the site and use of or reliance on such advice, opinion, statement or other information is at your own risk.
ONLINE COMMERCE
Wines & Vines may allow you to purchase different types of products and services online that are provided by Wines & Vines. Wines & Vines is not responsible for the quality, accuracy, timeliness, reliability or any other aspect of these products and services. You agree to be financially responsible for all purchases made by you or someone acting on your behalf through the site. You agree to use the site and to purchase services or products through the site for legitimate, non-commercial purposes only. You agree to only purchase goods or services for yourself or for another person for whom you are legally permitted to do so. When making a purchase for a third party that requires you to submit the third party's personal information to Wines & Vines, you represent that you have obtained the express consent of such third party to provide such third party's personal information.
USE OF WINERY, PHONEBOOK and BUYER'S GUIDE DIRECTORIES
The information contained in any company directories that may be provided on the site is provided for business lookup purposes and this information may not be copied or redistributed.
INTERACTIVE FEATURES
The site may include a variety of features, such as blogs, comments, and email services, that allow feedback to Wines & Vines and real-time interaction between users and other features, such as e-mail services, that allow users to communicate with others. You are responsible for material that you post on comments, blogs and other public posting areas on the site. Wines & Vines does routinely reviews the messages, information or files that others may provide through the site. It is a condition of your use of the site that you do not:
Restrict or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Sites.
Post or transmit any unlawful, threatening, abusive, libelous, fraudulent, false, defamatory, discriminatory, obscene, vulgar, hateful, pornographic, profane or indecent information of any kind, including without limitation any transmissions constituting or encouraging conduct that would constitute a criminal offense, give rise to civil liability or otherwise violate any local, state, national or international law.
Post or transmit any information, software or other material that violates or infringes upon the rights of others, including material that is an invasion of privacy or publicity rights or that is protected by copyright, trademark or other proprietary right, or derivative works with respect thereto, without first obtaining permission from the owner or right holder.
Post or transmit any information, software or other material that contains a virus or other harmful component.
Post, transmit or in any way exploit any information, software or other material for commercial purposes, or that contains advertising.
Advertise or solicit to anyone to buy or sell products or services, or to make donations of any kind, without the express written approval of Wunes & Vines.
Gather for the purpose of spamming, phishing or password harvesting email addresses that have been posted by other users of the site.
Use or attempt to use another person's account, password or services.
Disrupt, interfere with or otherwise violate the security of the site or any services, accounts, passwords, servers or networks related to the Sites.
Send repeated messages to another user or repeat postings of the same message under the same or multiple subjects.
A VIOLATION OF THE FOREGOING MAY BE REFERRED TO LAW ENFORCEMENT
You understand that Wines & Vines has no obligation to monitor any comments, blogs, or other areas of the sites through which users can supply information or material. Wines & Vines reserves the right at all times to disclose any information as necessary to satisfy any law, regulation or governmental request, or to refuse to post or to remove any information or materials, in whole or in part, that in Wines & Vines' sole discretion are objectionable or in violation of these Terms of Use.
INDEMNIFICATION
YOU AGREE TO INDEMNIFY, DEFEND AND HOLD HARMLESS, WINES AND VINES AND ITS PARTNERS, AFFILIATES, SUPPLIERS, LICENSORS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, SHAREHOLDERS, EMPLOYEES, REPRESENTATIVES, CONTRACTORS, AGENTS AND CONTENT PROVIDERS FROM ANY AND ALL CLAIMS, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, CLAIMS FOR DEFAMATION, TRADE DISPARAGEMENT, PRIVACY AND INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY INFRINGEMENT, AND DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ATTORNEYS' FEES, ARISING FROM OR RELATING TO 1) CONTENT OR INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE; 2) Wines & Vines' USE OF INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE; 3) INFORMATION OR MATERIAL POSTED OR TRANSMITTED THROUGH YOUR PASSWORD ACCOUNT, EVEN IF NOT POSTED OR TRANSMITTED BY YOU; AND 4) ANY VIOLATION OF THIS TERMS OF USE BY YOU.
TERMINATION
Wines & Vines may terminate or restrict your use of the site or any part of the site at any time for any reason without notice. In the event of termination, you are no longer authorized to access the part of the site affected by such termination or restriction.
MISCELLANEOUS
This Terms of Use constitutes the entire agreement between Wines & Vines and you with respect to the subject matter contained in this Terms of Use and supersedes all previous and contemporaneous agreements, proposals and communications, written or oral. You also may be subject to additional terms and conditions that may apply when you use the products or services of a third party that are provided through the Sites. These Terms of Use shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of California without giving effect to any of its conflicts of law provisions. You agree that any cause of action relating to your use of the site must be filed in the state or federal courts located in San Rafael, California. Wines & Vines may transfer its rights and obligations under the Terms of Use at any time without notice. If any provision of these Terms of Use shall be held to be unlawful, void or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from these Terms of Use and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. Any failure of Wines & Vines to enforce or exercise any provision of these Terms of Use shall not constitute a waiver of that right or provision. In the event of termination of these Terms of Use for any reason, the provisions entitled License To Wines & Vines, Disclaimers And Limitation Of Liability, Indemnification, Interactive Features, and other provisions for which survival is equitable or appropriate, shall survive.
Products
Wine Analytics Report
Industry Databases
Buyer's Guide
Wines & Vines Directory
Subscribe
Wine Analytics Report
Wines & Vines Directory
Terms of Service | Privacy Policy
Copyright © 2001-2020 by Wine Communications Group, Inc. All Rights Reserved. No material may be reproduced without written permission of the Publisher.
Cookies required for full site functionality. Click for guide to enable. CLOSE
